I will call me, people are continuously
coming forward to help each other, in this sequence
many banking sectors are also coming forward to help,
Ashwin,
after the order of Siwan District Officer, Siwan branch of ICICI Bank donated
masks and about 75 liters of hand sanitizer to the district administration for the migrant laborers coming from outside so
that it can be used
for the poor migrant laborers coming from outside.
On this occasion, the branch manager of Siwan ICICI Bank and
other colleagues were present.
We handed over these masks
and 75 liters of bottles on behalf of the bank which the
district administration needs and
in the global pandemic due to the pandemic, we are making more and more
available from the bank, but
this will be distributed among the people who had just given it to the district administration. It was
discussed that a train is coming
from Delhi, there are 16 trains, so
how should the union be given my name,
leadership like yours should be given to whom will
this be given to the workers, right now you people are limited to this much